Bye.
Don't cross the Yeongdongdaegyo Bridge.
Stay in Gangbuk today.
-You drive.
-Okay!
-The seat belt.
-Okay.
-Done?
-Not yet. Done.
Okay. I'm moving off.
-Go. Okay.
-Let's go.
What's wrong?
Wait, my foot.
Your foot?
EPISODE 7
-Someone's calling to move your car.
-Okay…
Hello?
Oh, okay.
Get some more sleep.
I'm sorry. Sorry about that.
Did he get a new car?
I… Wait, no. Why… I can't breathe.
But I can't breathe… Oh, wait!
Why would you choke me?
You know the overwhelming force
of cuteness?
It makes you want to pinch it
and hold it until it can't breathe.
Like a puppy, a kitten, and a cub.
I know I'm as cute as they are.
Exactly.
Oh, my. Wait. I can't breathe.
Oh, right.
Shoot. I'm going to be late for work.
Hey, Kyeong-do.
Don't go to work. Stay with me. Please?
You're heavy.
You should prepare for the new job, too.
Just for today. Please?
Hey, I said you're heavy.
Please?
Intern.
Have you checked
this movie's release date?
Yes.
Send it to the manager.
She told me to upload it
if you confirm it.
"If the great assistant manager
approves it, just publish it."
That's what she said.
Still, let's show her one more time
before we upload it.
Okay.
Where's Kim Doo-jin?
He probably went
to the Midlife Cop press conference.
Did he have to go so early?
Fuck!
Gotcha, you brat. Wait right there.
Gosh, how did he know I was here?
The corporate card?
My personal card.
Did you think I'd give up
if you avoided me?
I wasn't avoiding you.
I came here to work.
Three hours before the press conference?
What are you doing here?
You're a little too high up to be here.
I'm here to catch you, you punk.
I even gave up on my lunch hour
to be here.
So why? Why is that?
An Da-hye. Why did you start covering her?
It's wrong for a reporter to demand
another reporter to reveal the informant.
It's suspicious.
Why is An Da-hye looking for you?
And why are you avoiding me?
That's because you're hiding something.
That's not it. I was covering it honestly.
And besides, you can't do this.
You're taking it personally
because she's your ex.
What do you mean, "No"?
My current girlfriend.
Oh, that day.
When Seo Ji-woo said in the lobby
she was wearing your underwear…
I knew there was something.
Same here.
I think there is something going on.
I'm personally very curious.
I'll keep it to myself. Who was it?
But--
INCOMING CALL
SEO JI-YEON
Answer your phone.
It's your sister-in-law.
Keep acting cheeky,
and you'll be in big trouble.
Yes, hello?
Yes.
Isn't Excel one of the basic skills?
I'm learning, but it's too hard.
You're learn…
If you keep doing this,
they won't stop calling you a free rider.
Okay.
"Okay"?
-It's not "okay." You--
-We have a guest.
Hello. Ms. Seo will be here shortly.
-I'll have you wait inside.
-Okay.
Bring tea.
What would you like to drink?
Well, a hot Americano will do.
Shit. How much longer
do I have to keep this up?
How long do I have to
put up with that old fossil?
Thank you.
Wait, why are you drinking that?
I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking--
That's Ms. Seo's.
Why would you drink that?
I'm sorry about that,
but why would you get so upset over this?
Sorry about that. The meeting ran over.
No, I just got here too.
Ms. Seo, I'll bring you new coffee.
Kang Min-woo…
Your husband was the informant?
Yes.
But why…
But it only makes sense
if he can benefit from it.
What would he get
from getting rid of Cho Jin-eon?
With him present,
it's hard for him to sell the company.
The executives were complimenting Jin-eon
for his performance.
Sell the company?
That's the reason he's pretending
to ignore my illness as well.
He's not interested
in running the company.
He'll reveal my illness
at a crucial moment
and make people think that there's no one
to run the company.
Then he'll step forward
to sell the company.
Because once I lose all my memories,
he'll be my representative.
It seems he's already found a buyer.
My goodness. He's a real scary guy.
Then Ji-woo…
That's why I'm worried.
Ji-woo will have to go through all this.
I'm worried.
I even wonder if I'm being selfish.
I'm worried
if Ji-woo could put up with all this.
I feel bad for her, and I pity her.
Is this why you haven't told her yet?
If she finds out that I have dementia,
Ji-woo will fall apart.
Now that I've talked to her in person,
it turns out she's relying on me so much
when I'm not so reliable.
If there's anything I can help you with,
I'll do my best.
About the secretary
who was just here earlier.
You mean Secretary Yoo?
Yes, did she join the company
through an open recruitment?
Why do you ask?
Because I think
I heard her being a free rider.
She graduated
from my father-in-law's school.
My husband recommended her.
Can you get me a change of clothes?
Yes, ma'am. I'll prepare it right away.
Wait, why are you drinking that?
That's Ms. Seo's.
Why would you drink that?
So I can drink it later.
This place makes good coffee.
I'll ask her to make a new one--
Oh, no. This will do.
What were you thinking to show up here?
I can't do this.
How long do I have to do this for?
The chief secretary is driving me crazy.
You didn't anticipate this?
That as well, but this is too dangerous.
What if Ms. Seo ends up dying?
What is that drug?
If this goes wrong,
I'll end up going to prison.
Lower your voice.
Why don't you be more direct?
You want more money.
Okay. Go back to work.
And...
don't you ever come here.
Because your second phone is off--
If you have anything to say, text me.
I'll check more often.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Hey, Seong-sik.
When you did the article about juice,
where did you get the analysis done?
Oh, really? Can you send me the link?
Yeah, thanks.
Here.
Can you analyze any elements
that are harmful,
or would induce illnesses,
or anything that is not found
in ordinary coffee?
Sure, I'll do that.
Well, how long is it going to take?
Normally, it takes about
two to three weeks.
Okay, then...
I have to write an article.
So if you could rush a bit…
Please?
Okay, I'll try my best.
Okay, thank you.
SUBWAY EXIT
FLOWERS
Hello.
Mom.
Well, thanks.
You've never done this before.
I told you a million times
that I like flowers,
but you only got me carnations.
I remembered it today.
-Next time, buy half of these.
-Okay.
Go.
Mom, where are you headed?
Tuesday service.
Why does she keep taking this route?
Where did you get the flowers?
-My son got them for me.
-You raised him well.
I fed him mostly rice,
and he grew up well.
Beer is the best with pizza.
SPARKLING WATER
That is impossible.
-Exactly.
-Right?
Here.
By the way, I found a flower shop
on my way home.
I've never noticed it,
but it's been there for four years.
What, you're hinting
that you've never been in a relationship?
Apparently, orange roses exist.
You should've bought one.
One? I bought 20.
What?
-They were taken away instantly.
-Damn it, by which jerk?
My mom.
Hey, come here.
Bring your face over here.
You're a reporter.
Don't leave out the subject when you talk.
Why are you so sensitive?
No, it's just…
You know...
-Listen to me.
-Okay.
I was told to take a photo
for the press release.
But what is this?
It's a good picture.
But it looks unnatural.
What is good about this typical pose?
What do you want then?
You know, like this, right?
I'm on my way to work, I turn around,
and snap. I turn around, and snap.
Just like that.
You know what I mean, right?
No? Right?
Yeah, you mean like,
the daughters-in-law of major corporations
attending a wedding?
Yes, exactly!
What is this boring picture? Gosh…
Shall we go out?
Let's take a few on Teheran-ro.
So I was thinking…
Yes?
I'm going to the company
to meet my sister before I start.
You should take a picture of me then.
Just keep taking candid pictures.
Then we might get a good one.
Me? The assistant manager
of Dongwoon Daily?
Yes, you.
Then how are you going to get there?
By taxi? That's weird.
Taxi? Oh, right. That's kind of unnatural.
But if I drive…
I can't get it valet-parked.
I should've listened to my sister
when she said she'd assign me a chauffeur.
Dang, a director even gets a chauffeur?
Why did you say no?
It's convenient to have a chauffeur.
Not convenient at all. It's suffocating
to be with a stranger in a car.
I'd get carsick.
Hey, just use this. It's a good picture.
You look like you'll work like a cow.
"Moo, the director is working. Moo."
"Give me work. Moo."
What?
You open your mouth.
You open first. You first.
Then… Oh, wait.
Hey, Jeong-min.
Me?
Well, I'm home. I'm chilling.
You're chilling with Ji-woo.
We're having dinner together.
Both of you, come to Woo-sik's place now.
Now?
Jeong-min, hello?
-What's that about?
-What?
He said to come now.
Who are you to fool me?
"Yes, Jeong-min. Yes. I'm chilling.
I'm home." That was too awkward.
You know Kyeong-do can't do method acting.
When he said, "Oh, Jeong-min,"
I knew right away that he was with Ji-woo.
Right. Why did you stutter? Do you feel
uncomfortable getting back together?
When did I talk like that?
Is Uncle Kyeong-do going out with you?
-Don't we look good together?
-Date for a long time without fighting.
Sure.
We will. Thanks.
We should have some soju, no?
This annoying little couple. Right?
This pairs well with whiskey too.
Just feel free to drink. I won't come here
if you keep doing this.
Still, you idiot.
If you say that,
I'll find this in my bag. Look…
Drink it alone at home.
Whiskey pairs well with solitude.
I knew Se-yeong was the only loyal friend.
When I was in the army,
she was the only one who visited me.
You guys never came. Only bought me drinks
when I was out on a break.
Hey, this is really good.
You went to meet him alone?
-Yes.
-Why?
Oh, well, just to see
if Kyeong-do was doing okay.
I was worried. That's why. Is it good?
But we didn't even get to meet, did we?
What? Yeah, right.
Because I had to drive the commander.
So, why were you curious
about Kyeong-do's condition?
Hey, what kind of question is that?
What are you trying to say?
Were you worried about him that much?
This is serious. When things get serious,
you become curious. Do you want this?
At the time,
he got wasted and returned to his base
early in the morning.
That's when. You eat it.
A day like that happened a lot.
It's normal to be curious.
No, oh, seriously.
It was the day of Ji-yeon's wedding!
Don't you remember?
WINTER, 2009
I never asked you for a favor.
Switch with me just once, please?
But I booked a concert ticket.
I'll pay for the ticket. And I'll take you
to another one when we're discharged.
No way. Never.
I'll take your driving shift next weekend.
Wait. I'll drive every weekend this month.
What do you say? Are you in?
-For real?
-For real.
Okay.
After your sister's wedding,
we might as well visit Kyeong-do
while you're here.
Do you think he'd be happy to see me?
He'd get pissed off and desert the army.
Then by chance… by any chance,
if Kyeong-do's out on a break?
If he happens to be out
on the day of your sister's wedding,
let's meet him. Okay?
That's worth trying.
Did you tell him that I was coming?
No!
Se-yeong.
Don't look at me like that.
That gives me butterflies in the stomach.
Do you
want me to get back with Kyeong-do?
You know what?
I think everyone
should have a good breakup.
That way, they're either sad or relieved.
But you and Kyeong-do?
It's not a matter of
getting back together.
I want you to break up properly.
You're really eloquent, Se-yeong.
Like a teacher.
I don't understand a thing.
Focus.
Hello. Can you show me your invitation?
Oh, the invitation, sir?
You cannot enter without an invitation.
Oh, okay, sir.
Here, cheers!
Drink.
Are you sure Ji-woo's back in Korea?
How come she wasn't at the wedding?
Maybe there was a separate entrance
for the family. The hotel was huge.
Hey, how did you know
Ji-woo's sister was getting married?
Did you read the article?
No, Se-yeong told me
there was an article about it.
That Ji-woo might come.
I mean, there is no way to reach her.
It'd be nice to run into her like this.
Even from Ji-woo's point of view,
it'd be worth the long flight.
Right. It'd be nice to see him
while she's here.
Then, shall we call JARIM Apparel?
That we'd like to know
the second daughter's contact information?
What do you think?
I'm just saying because I feel for him.
Don't be so serious.
My goodness.
Anyway, when are you two joining the army?
When I'm discharged,
you should go right away.
I'll take care of her.
Who are you to take care of Se-yeong?
Do you like Park Se-yeong?
I ship it.
Hey, if you two start dating,
Chaos is doomed, you know?
It's enough with Lee Kyeong-do
and Seo Ji-woo. Right, Se-yeong? Yeah?
Then we shouldn't break up.
This asshole… He's serious.
Kyeong-do, get up.
See the look in his eyes?
I'm glad I'm out on a break.
This is so worth it.
Worth it, my ass!
This is harmful, Woo-sik.
Think about it carefully.
Hey! You asshole, you're too drunk.
What the hell is wrong with him? Hey.
If you drink this, we're going out.
Wait, what the hell?
Look at them. What are you…
Hey, we only met because of theater.
This club was only meant for theater.
This club wasn't for dating.
You idiot.
Why the hell are you snickering?
Congratulations, sir.
What? Don't be ridiculous.
Are you here to date?
You assholes… Just me alone…
What, is this a dating republic or what?
Cheers!
SE-YEONG
Hey, Se-yeong.
No, I was about to get up.
Yeah. Why didn't you come yesterday?
Everyone was waiting for you.
I was with my family until late.
I see. Are you in the hotel?
Yes.
Now that Ji-yeon isn't home,
you're not going home at all?
Did Kyeong-do get home safely last night?
I hope so? He was probably with
Woo-sik and Jeong-min last night.
I see.
Se-yeong.
Where is Kyeong-do stationed?
BAEKGEOM BASE
CHECKPOINT
VISITOR REQUEST
NAME: LEE KYEONG-DO
Wait. You cannot visit
Sergeant Lee Kyeong-do today, ma'am.
-Why not?
-He's on an off-base dispatch.
CHECKPOINT
MILITARY BASE ENTRANCE
Hey, Se-yeong. It's me, Kyeong-do.
Did you happen to visit me today?
I was told that a girl my age visited,
but he doesn't know the name.
Was it you?
Oh, yes. It was me.
Really? But we met yesterday.
Well, since you drank a lot.
I was worried.
Worried if you were struggling
because you didn't see Ji-woo.
I just went to check on you.
It's only your second day with Woo-sik.
I'm causing you trouble.
Right. Hey, speaking of which…
I was too drunk.
Kyeong-do, do you think
I'm making the right choice?
What if my life is doomed?
Hey, that hurts.
Then explain that sweet look in your eyes
last night.
Woo-sik is kind of cute.
Yeah, right. You make a good couple.
Happy? That I went to the wedding
to see you and got kicked out?
Yes, I'm so damn happy.
I'm so damn happy too.
Because it was actually me
who visited you?
Yes.
Come here.
Artist Choi is in a relationship, right?
Gosh.
Why would you cut in without a blinker?
You startled me.
They already broke up, right?
It feels like this scandal is too late.
I don't know. I'd like to know as well.
If you cover it,
promise me to let me know, okay?
You're good.
With the CEO title and a bigger paycheck,
you're not feeling up to it?
Excuse me.
Hello?
Yeah, I'm eating right now.
Have you had lunch yet?
I already have.
Do you want to come home tonight?
I'll boil a whole Korean chicken,
but it's too much for us.
Leftovers always end up in the trash.
It's nice to eat together when it's hot.
I love baeksuk.
But I have to cover
a movie press conference tonight.
Leave some for me, Mom.
I'll eat it tomorrow.
Baeksuk is still tasty
even when it's reheated.
Yes. I'll call you. Yeah. Enjoy.
What movie press conference?
As far as I know, there's nothing tonight.
Eat.
Wait. I'm smelling something.
It's the jjajangmyeon smell.
Yeah, keep eating.
It's not this smell, though.
Does he have work?
Yeah, I guess he's going somewhere
for an article.
Why are you worried about Kyeong-do
so much lately?
I'm not worried about him.
Not many sons buy their moms flowers.
Do you think he bought them for me?
He bought them for the person he likes.
Wait. If you knew, why did you take them?
What else? How was I supposed to ask him?
"Is someone at home?
Why are you buying flowers after work?"
Was I supposed to ask? And embarrass him?
Right, you have a point. My goodness.
If it withers again…
He'd be heartbroken.
I'm worried about that.
Back then, I was ill.
That probably made it worse.
ORGANIZATION CHART
She is our lead designer,
Department Manager Ji Yeon-soo.
She worked with Dad for a long time.
It's important
to make her your person first.
She will help you a lot.
She was born in 1974. Okay.
Don't just look at the pictures.
Next is…
Yes. Executive Director Choi.
You need to watch out for her a little.
-Is she a villain?
-No.
She's not like that.
Then why do I need to watch out?
Should I say she's on the border?
She doesn't care about loyalty
or comradeship.
Her priority is her own benefit.
So she's made contributions
to the company.
Between a villain and a helper. Okay.
I plan to release the press release
the day after tomorrow.
-Do you feel pressured?
-No, that's not it.
I just don't really like that picture.
Do you want me to get a new photographer?
No worries. It'll be the same anyway.
They'll make me turn slightly on the chair
and smile like this.
What is that?
Oh, gosh.
Is that how I look also?
-Is it from the same place?
-Yes.
Kind of.
I look like a cow who'd only work.
Right? Excuse me.
Sure.
LEE KYEONG-DO
Hey, I'm at work.
Wow, so cool. "I'm at work." Dang.
I'm busy, so I have to go.
I'll call you back.
I sounded pretty cool, right?
Director Seo.
Gosh.
What are you doing here?
Well… Because I missed you?
This feels so nice, Kyeong-do.
Are you coming from work?
No, I'm coming from your house.
What? Then you should've stayed home.
You must be tired.
There are days
I feel like I have to pick you up.
For example?
A day like today?
What is a day like today?
That prick who should be turned down
by all the door locks in the world.
What?
What the hell?
Shit. Hey! Fuck.
What are you doing?
So laid-back.
Some might think this is your house.
Because I'm done flirting.
What are you doing at other people's home?
The door code. Did you change it?
Why do you care who changed it?
What matters is
that you're violating the law.
-This is a crime.
-Hey! Fuck.
Will you press the button?
Hey, I know you set me up with An Da-hye
to get me divorced.
You got rid of me to approach Seo Ji-woo!
I want to show off that I was the one
who tried to stop the article.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why would I listen
to a trash reporter like you?
If I were you,
I'd look into the informant first.
Besides, let's use honorifics from now on.
We're not close.
Being casual with you gives me goosebumps.
Right. Yes. Right.
Yeah, the informant.
Jeez.
I get it. It was Seo Ji-woo.
Gosh.
I'm onto you two. I heard
Seo Ji-woo's working at the company now.
I'll send both of you to hell
as soon as I can. You hear me?
I said use honorifics.
You're not fucking listening.
You son of a--
I wouldn't even set up a blind date
for a dick like you.
Such a loser.
Fuck.
What is this?
Give it to her.
You have to be
straightforward with him, okay?
He kept pressing the door code
as if this were his house. That jackass…
That was the real reason
you felt like you had to pick me up.
-Right?
-No!
You're yelling, so I'm right.
Probably not.
Is he out of his mind?
What is it? What did that lunatic say?
-Can I have any privacy?
-Not on this.
"My second proposal to you!"
That son of a bitch!
Wow, this guy's got no brain.
Is divorce a joke?
So cringe. A second proposal?
I should've punched that prick
in the throat, shit.
Hey, I can't let this slide.
Give me his number.
You won't be able to do it.
I'll meet him and draw the line clearly.
I'll meet him and return it.
Why? Just call a quick delivery service.
You can't find this in Korea.
Things will get worse if it got lost.
Wow.
This guy knew what he was doing. Right?
He knew if he got you something expensive,
he'd get to see you again.
He calculated it.
Have you ever seen a dog with rabies?
No!
I think I'm seeing one now.
This is how he is.
Once he's fixated on something,
he decides he's right.
Still, I feel a little bad
for my Kyeong-do.
You must've been upset to be given this.
Still, I got under his skin.
I covered it when I punched the door code.
I bet he was upset.
Come here.
Where can you buy that?
I don't know.
How much is it?
Come here.
Don't move for five minutes.
I need to recharge.
SUMMER, 2015
This design is popular for matching rings.
This has diamonds,
so the ladies prefer this.
Do you have anything simple?
If the jewels are too flashy…
How about this?
I'll take this.
Do you know her size?
Do you see the knot?
Excellent.
Aren't you tired? Do you want to go home?
I'm okay. Do you want me
to get something to drink?
No, I've already had enough.
Hey, how about a drive this weekend?
-No.
-Why not?
This Saturday…
we're going to a fancy restaurant.
Really? What? Where?
I found a nice Korean restaurant.
Why? Is it some kind of an anniversary?
A day to have great food.
Great food…
Hey, Mom.
Dad? How serious?
Which hospital? Okay. Bye.
FRAGILE
Maybe he's still high from the drugs.
What's this bullshit, a second proposal?
What does he take Ji-woo for?
You don't treat someone right
when they're with you.
Once they're gone, running after them
just makes you sweat.
If he was nice to her when he had her,
these two wouldn't be together.
Read the room, please.
What I'm saying is,
am I the only one who doesn't understand
that asshole's second proposal?
That is my question.
Reunited couples can be happy.
Damn it.
Get her a gift too.
-Something impactful.
-Out of nowhere? Like a loser?
Did you get her anything for the job?
That's a good reason.
I already did.
I got her acupressure slippers.
-Wow.
-Acu… Acupressure, my ass.
Seriously, you're hopeless.
This isn't going to work.
I'll talk to my dad.
Get her an imported car or a sports car.
Okay? I'll give you
a long installment plan.
I won't attract her
with something expensive like him.
Seriously. Damn it.
Is that right?
For how many months?
You little…
Hurry up.
You… wait. Okay, where's my phone?
SEO JI-WOO
Are you at work?
You said you might work overtime,
so I thought you might still be at work.
No, I'm on my way home.
Okay. Have fun. Bye.
Ms. Seo Ji-woo?
I'm Jin Han-kyeong.
I work with Assistant Manager Lee.
I've seen many pictures of you,
but we've never met in person.
Hello.
Assistant Manager Lee left.
Yes. I just talked to him on the phone.
Okay.
If you don't mind, can we have some tea?
I've been working with him
since we were in the Culture Team.
Yes. I've heard.
I've also heard that you go to
his mother's laundromat for her kimchi.
That's right.
With all due respect, let me say this.
I'm actually
a little disappointed.
Assistant Manager Lee… No, Kyeong-do.
Every time he makes a crucial decision
in his life, he is let down.
It turns out
you were the reason every time.
In the past, when you got back together
and broke up again,
he was waiting to be assigned
to the Current Affairs Team.
He really wanted it, and I also think
it was more suitable for him.
I don't know what happened exactly
between you two,
but Kyeong-do…
Well, he was in so much pain.
And as he was on leave,
the transfer was canceled.
Let me overstep a little more.
This time, it was a chance
to have training in Chicago.
The competition rate was 100 to 1,
but he was rewarded for his big exclusive.
And he turned it down
and gave the chance to another reporter.
I know I'm overstepping my boundary,
but there's something
you need to know, Ji-woo.
Kyeong-do has always had
the highest priority.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
This is something I really needed to know.
Thank you for telling me.
Thank you…
for your understanding.
Does Jeong-min's father
import cars from abroad?
Yes.
I think he will later close
his used car shop and work for him.
So? Is he getting you a lot of discounts?
He said he'd get me
a long installment plan.
You know what he said when I told him
that I got you acupressure slippers?
He said I was hopeless.
Are you busy at work?
By the way, I returned the ring safely.
You were right.
There's nothing good in seeing him again.
You did the right thing.
Was that a limited edition or something?
I'll get you one.
Before I turn 80.
Kyeong-do.
Is something wrong?
I can't ask you why you didn't go.
I can't tell you
not to give up on good opportunities
because of me.
I'm dead happy that you're next to me.
I feel like I'm finally living my life.
So…
I'm happy…
that you're not…
going to Chicago.
Aren't I awful?
I feel so relieved
to hear that you're happy.
Let's go.
What's wrong with him?
Hey, Kyeong-do. Have you seen my car key?
I don't know.
What? Where did it go?
Where the heck is it?
Man, not here.
But it's got to be here.
Hey, come on. Let's go.
No, wait. Where?
Hurry. Come on.
But why? Where are we going?
Where is the car key?
It's way too early,
and I haven't even washed my face.
Where are you taking me?
Tell me where we're going at least.
Mr. Kim!
Ji-woo, I want to get you imported cars
or limited edition luxury items,
but get them yourself.
You're rich.
But I'll find you a world
that you'll like.
Ji-woo.
Are you okay?
The last bus has left.
Oh, that's okay.
Let's go, come on. Be careful. Let's go.
There.
The informant was Kang Min-woo.
And you avoided me because you hated
the thought of me finding out?
Don't accuse me.
I didn't know that you, Seo Ji-woo,
and Cho Jin-eon were involved.
Her mom had her from an affair.
Can you believe that?
She needs our help,
so we should cooperate.
Kyeong-do is right before my eyes.
I can't tell my heart not to fall for him.
That's why couples elope at night.
Why do you need my passport?
I guess Dad wanted to see
this side of you, Ji-woo.
I can do it.
Let's get into trouble.